Some fight. Others fall. All are heroes.
Leningrad is a war, drama film directed by Aleksandr Buravskiy.
When in 1941 Nazi Germany invaded the Soviet Union,
their troops quickly besieged Leningrad.
Foreign journalists are evacuated but one of them, Kate
Davies, is presumed dead and misses the plane.
Alone in the city she is helped by Nina Tsvetnova a young and idealist police officer and together they
will fight for their own survival and the survival of the people in the besieged Leningrad.
Philip Parker, played by Gabriel Byrne.
Kate Davis, played by Mira Sorvino.
von Leeb, played by Armin Mueller-Stahl.
Walter Hoesdorff, played by Alexander Beyer.
Vinkelmeyer, played by Christian Berkel.
Adolf Hitler, played by Eckehard Hoffmann.
Attack on Leningrad, or just Leningrad, is a 2009 war film written and
directed by Aleksandr Buravsky, set during the Siege of Leningrad.
The film explores themes of journalist, world war ii, wolf's
lair, st. petersburg, russia, restaurant critic.
The tone is emotional.